

(905) 324-4616

✓ Niagara Falls, ON, Canada

⊕ dt

dbutko.com

Quality Assurance Engineer

Summary

Quality-focused ISTQB Certified QA Engineer with two years of experience in Manual and Automation Testing in accounting and medical industries. Graduated from Centennial College in Canada with Diploma in Computer Science. Built and organized QA Department for the medical project and successfully supported more than 25 customers.

Education

Centennial College, Canada

2021 - 2022

Diploma (Software Engineering Technician)

ISTQB Certificate 2020

International Software Testing Qualifications Board

Belarussian Technological University

Bachelor's Degree (Accounting, analysis and audit) 2011

Experience

Rovensys | Poland-USA

remedly.com

Jun 2020 -Dec 2021

QA Engineer

- Created and organized QA Department, mentored four QAs
- Developed test strategy and test plan for the project
- Tested integration with insurance companies, ERP, RCM, EHR, Patient Portal, billing, and payment systems
- Prepared and implemented test cases for automation testing.
- Supported and communicated with more than 25 customers.
- Participated in architecture decisions, communicated with a cross-functional team, and worked closely with the Product Manager and 17 developers

Freelance Task Flow | Poland-Canada taskflowapp.com

Feb 2021 -Dec 2021

Mobile QA Engineer

- Created test plan and strategy for the project
- Tested application for iPhone, iPad, and Mac
- Participated in releases and supported customers

EPAM Systems | Belarus

Aug 2014 -Feb 2020

epam.com

Senior Accountant Europe

- · Worked in the lead IT Company in Belarus
- Automated accounting tasks and decreased task execution time from 2 days to 30 minutes
- Prepared month and year reports for eight EU Epam companies
- Created tasks for developers for automation in SAP

BDO International | Belarus

Dec 2012 -Apr 2014

bdo.com

Audit Assistant

· Provided internal and IFRS audit for government projects

Deloitte | Belarus

deloitte.com

Dec 2011 -Nov 2012

Acountant

 Performed the whole cycle of financial operations according to IFRS in SAP for the lead Audit company

Skills

Technical Skills

- · Manual Testing, Regression testing, Smoke Testing
- Automation testing, Selenium WebDriver, PyTest
- REST API Testing, Postman
- · C#, Java, Python, JavaScript
- SQL, PL/SQL, MongoDB
- · Web Development: (Node.is. Angular)
- Artificial Intelligence (Python)
- Jira, TestRail, AzureDevops, Git
- Communication. Highly responsible for the deadlines and team arrangements. Strong oral and written communication skills.
- **Productivity.** Demanding to my own productivity, over the years, I developed skills necessary for focused work under tight deadlines. Time tracker, focused sessions, checklists, shortcuts are some of the tools I always use.
- **Self Education.** Constantly self-educating on weekdays from 5 a.m. to 7 a.m., reading articles and books. Documenting knowledge in Notion for future reference saves me time and helps digest new information.

Projects



Remedly remedly.com



Portfolio dbutko.com



Task Flow taskflowapp.com



Quick Brain quickbrain.com

Other Skills

Hard-working Self-studying English C1 Attention to detail Time-management Diploma IFRS